<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
   <results>
      <result>
         <description>Reynald P.C.: The best damn pizza in all of the greater New York City! I've been eating here since I was in elementary school and the pizza is ...</description>
         <title>The 15 Best Places for Pizza in Queens - Foursquare</title>
         <url>https://foursquare.com/top-places/queens/best-places-pizza</url>
      </result>
      <result>
         <description>Menu, hours, photos, and more for Queens Blvd Pizzeria Inc. located at 8904 Queens Blvd, Elmhurst, NY, 11373-4932, offering Pizza, Italian, Dinner, Pasta, ...</description>
         <title>Queens Blvd Pizzeria Inc. Menu - Elmhurst, NY Restaurant</title>
         <url>https://menupages.com/queens-blvd-pizzeria-inc/8904-queens-blvd-elmhurst</url>
      </result>
      <result>
         <description>Pizza is a savory dish of Italian origin, consisting of a usually round, flattened base of leavened wheat-based dough topped with tomatoes, cheese, and various ...</description>
         <title>Pizza - Wikipedia</title>
         <url>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pizza</url>
      </result>
      <result>
         <description>New York City's pizza scene is stronger than ever. Find out where to go for the best pizza restaurants and what they serve on their pies.</description>
         <title>Best pizza in New York City: Where to go and what they serve</title>
         <url>https://www.cnn.com/travel/article/best-pizza-new-york-city/index.html</url>
      </result>
      <result>
         <description>Scott's Pizza Tours. Menu; Tour Descriptions · Private Events · Pizzerias · Blog · Tour Photos ... Discover the secrets of real NYC Pizza! Tour by foot · Tour by bus ...</description>
         <title>Scott's Pizza Tours | New York City Guided Pizza Tasting ... - NYC</title>
         <url>http://www.scottspizzatours.com/</url>
      </result>
      <result>
         <description>Enjoy authentic Italian quality pizza. Dough made fresh every day. Sauce from the original Giammarco recipe. Order online for delivery or carry-out.</description>
         <title>Marco's Pizza</title>
         <url>https://www.marcos.com/</url>
      </result>
      <result>
         <description>Blaze Pizza®, Fast-Fire'd®, the horizontal logo design, the round emblem design, the proprietary names "Pizzasmith", "Pizza'olo", "1 Top", "Simple Pie", "Red ...</description>
         <title>Blaze Pizza - Fast-Fire'd Custom Built Artisanal Pizzas</title>
         <url>https://blazepizza.com/</url>
      </result>
      <result>
         <description>Jet's makes pizza, wings and salads using quality ingredients and has over 380 locations in 20 states.</description>
         <title>Jet's Pizza: Pizza, Wings, and Salads</title>
         <url>https://www.jetspizza.com/</url>
      </result>
      <result>
         <description>Gourmet Pizzas (baked or take n bake), sandwiches, fresh salads and killer wings with on-time hot delivery, pick up or eat in.</description>
         <title>Extreme Pizza</title>
         <url>https://www.extremepizza.com/</url>
      </result>
      <result>
         <description>With over 45 years of experience, Hungry Howie's is consistently ranked as one of the top pizza franchises in the nation. From its humble beginnings outside of ...</description>
         <title>Hungry Howies | Home of the Original Flavored Crust® Pizza</title>
         <url>https://www.hungryhowies.com/</url>
      </result>
   </results>
